how old is the child now one year one year And
сейчас сколько ребёнку лет годик годик А
what to call one summer one summer Lev
как назвать одно лето одно лето Лев
called I mean Lev is a
назвал В смысле Лев это
Jewish name Lev Well damn, yes, something is wrong with me
ж еврейское имя Лев Ну блин да что-то я
Well, last year I didn't
малёха Ну я в прошлом году ещё не так
know how to call it now I wanted to
ведал как как сейчас я хотел Добрыня
call it Dobrynya but I called it Lev  Well, Lyova Well, I
назвать а назвал Лев Ну Лёва Да ну я
suggested different names, well, well,
разные имена предлагал как бы ну Ну и
well, well,
как
well, damn, I don't know, but
бы ну так блин не знаю да
baby, you've disappointed me.
малёха Ты меня
Hello, Hello, where are you
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте Вы
from in the north, where exactly is it from? Sur Rodnover,
откуда севера откуда именно сур родновер
Iglin, Iglin, Khinevich
иглин иглин Хиневич
Well, Danu Khinevich, bread, who do you support more,
Ну Дану Хиневич хлебо кого ты больше
little by little, everywhere
везде по чуть-чуть
Slavic Aryan Vedas read or are
славяно арийские веды читал или
you just fooling around I
балуешься
just realized that you find it
просто понял что тебе кажется
contradictory for example from them
противоречивым например из них
these flying objects there vimanas or whatever
эти летающие объекты там виманы или как
they are called or whatmans tma viry
они называются или ватманы тма виры
Yes I don't understand the question how do you perceive
Да не пойму вопрос как ты воспринимаешь
this reality or is it
это реальность или это
fiction of course reality each
выдумка конечно реальность каждая
subsequent civilization is less developed than the previous
последующее менее развита чем предыдущая
Yes  this is called degradation of tradition yes
Да это деградация традиции называются да
yes we are now actually living in the era of
ну да мы сейчас фактически живём в эпоху
Kali Yuga when Yes complete  where destruction
кали юга когда Да полная де разрушения
yes yes But look at yours The thing is
да да А вот смотри по твоим Дело в том
that I too yes I too am a representative of this
что я тоже да я тоже представитель этого
current of Inglings But I don't practice as much
течения инглингов Но я не так сильно как
I read Yes I read the
бы практикую Я читал Да читал
Slavic-Aryan Vedas I read an acquaintance with
славяно-арийские Веды читал знакомый с
three Lebo personally Yes I am not familiar with the Khi
трёх лебо лично Да с хи нечем не знаком
personally Yes Personally I met them in
лично Да Лично я встречался с ними в
Krasnodar like I'm originally from Rostov
Краснодаре типа я сам родом из Ростова
Yes but now I live in America 18 years in
Да но сейчас живу в Америке 18 лет через
2 years will be the twentieth to Khinevich in Omsk a
2 года будет двадцатое к Хиневич в Омск
long time ago Yes but it didn't
съездить ещё давно-давно Да но не
work out it was very far and then
получалось это очень далеко было а потом
I went to America  flew over here I can do this
я в Америку перелетел вот я это может
you know there are three left different
ещё знаете там у трёх лево разные
students can Pavel Globa
ученики может Павел Глоба
you know understood Eleanor of Aquitaine you don't
знаете понял Элеонора аквитанская её не
know her too
знаете тоже
divine girl such a very
божественная девушка такая очень
enlightened
просветная
Aquitaine
аквитанская
Pavel
Павел
Globa This is not the Globa that
Глоба Это не тот Глоба что
astro And look you have there
астро А смотрите Вы у вас есть там
some you there  conduct community Or are you
какое-то вы там проводите община Или вы
on your own in
сами по себе в
Surgut on
Сургуте сам по
your own when I lived in Rostov Yes, we
себе когда я жил в Ростове Да у нас в
had a lot of Inglings in Rostov and in  I don't know
Ростове было много инглингов а в не знаю
if they were in Surgut, but they were in KhMAO-Yugra
ли в Сургуте но в хмао-югре
Well, there are some, I know a couple of people there Well,
были Ну так есть я там пару человек знаю
not
Ну так не
really, because I see that your runes are
особо потому что я смотрю что у вас руны
just generic, that's normal, because
как раз родовые это нормально потому что
many have forgotten these signs now
многие сейчас забыли эти знаки
Oh, by the way, that swastika that
Да кстати да вот эту свастику которую
sem Hitler took this is also our
сем Гитлер взял это ж тоже наши
Slavic-Aryan symbols there are
славяно-арийские символы есть там есть
1488 types of swastikas absolutely different they
1488 видов свастик разных абсолютно они
are and octagonal eight-pointed
есть и восьмиугольные восьми конечные
bladed such three-bladed very
лопастные такие три лопастные очень
many Yes I think you know about such a
много Да я думаю вы знаете про такой
city as Arkaim Yes of course very many
город как Аркаим Да конечно очень много
here I am our Russian people  I ask yes Have
вот я наших русских людей спрашиваю да
you heard about the arches many have not
Вы слышали про арки многие нет потому
because history Yes you know what the
что историю Да вы знаете что означает
word
слово
history means
история
history history Yes it was the Jews who specially
история история Да это евреи специально
invented history for us Slavs Yes and the
придумали нам славянам историю Да и
name because it is from the Torah Yes And
назва потому что она из торы Да И вот
this is how many people eh the Great Prophet
это сколько людей э ещё Великий пророк
was I was his prophet  I call it Zadornov,
был я его пророком называю это Задорнов
you know, yes, he did a lot to popularize
вы же знаете Да он для популяризации
this
этой
our English theme,
э нашей инглингов ской темы очень много
yes, and when at first he told
сделал да И когда Сначала он рассказывал
people, proved about ra because ra
людям доказывал про ра потому что ра -
is  there was the sun god Ra le and the rainbow
это же был бог солнца Ра ле и радуга
why is this the arc of God Ra I tell my
почему это дуга Бога ра я рассказываю
friends They say no it's just a
знакомым Они говорят нет это просто
Rainbow I say explain then what is it
Радуга Я говорю объясни тогда что вот
like our ancestors took and came up with Rainbow is nothing
как наши предки взяли и придумали Радуга
but the arc of God joy
ни о чём а вот дуга Бога радость
prosperity ra yes
достаток ра да
Faith yes Faith -  this is to know ra and a fool
Вера да Вера - это ведать ра а дурак -
is one
Это тот
who has kind of lost ra lost
который как бы лишился ра лишился
wisdom yes a
мудрости да
lot yes But these And the British are
много да А вот эти А вот британцы это
also a kind of Slavs Aryans then who shaved their
тоже род славяна Ариев то которые брили
beards there is something like that well yes they are
бороды там что-то такое поэто ну да они
shaved they are shaved because they are shaved because they
бриты они Потому что бриты потому что
shaved  yes That's why they have these skinhead
брились да Поэтому у них вот эти скинхед
movements, these, this, that, all
движения вот эти вот это что тоже всё
this, yes Well, when I lived in Russia, I
это да Ну я я когда жил в России У меня
also had a beard, but here in America it's
тоже была борода но тут в Америке
a little bit not accepted. Yes, they
немножко как-то ну не принято Да меня
think that I'm some kind of Pakistani.  and
думают что я какой-то там пакистанец и
so on I try I shaved I yes
так дальше то я стараюсь я побрился я да
when I lived in Russia I had a beard
когда жил в России я с бородой был
because well a man without a beard Slavs
потому что ну мужчина без бороды славяна
Aryans are well like shaved and started
Арии это ну как бы бриты да начали
shaving  and you see these Anglo-Saxons
бриться и вот видишь эти англосаксы
in America they have this brand Trump is
они в Америке держат вот эту марку Трамп
not shaved Yes Musk is not shaved Biden is not
не бритый Да Маск не бритый байден не
shaved they all do not shave and our ancestors were
бритый они все не бреются а предки наши
like that the longer the beard the
такими чем длиннее борода больше был
wiser
мудре
the older the older and the
старой старе а
grandfather is so
дед такой
laid out he will do plastic surgery like a
выложенный пластическую операцию как
girl to look glamorous
девочка себе сделает чтоб гламурненько
be before there was a man it was a warrior
быть раньше был мужчина это был воин
a man like that with a beard like a Viking straight up
мужик такой да с бородой как Викинг прям
Slavic yes And now what are the
славяна да А сейчас что
glamorous guchi there
гучи гламурные там
glasses la Give me please
очечи ла Дай мне пожалуйста
in short and ratan
короче а ратан
washing machines dishwashers yes And by the way you
стиралки посудомойки да А кстати Вы же
know the calculation of the flight what
пролета исчисление знаете какой сейчас
year it is now according to the Yngling calendar
год по календарю инглингов
7533 And what  he is considered from the creation of
7533 А чего он считается от сотворения
the world in the Star Temple right And where
мира в Звёздном храме правильно А где
was this Star Temple not you are generally
этот был Звёздный храм не ты вообще
handsome you are great you know damn
красавчик ты молодец шаришь блин
Star Temple I don't
Звёздный храм Вот этого я не
know this where was it on the island of Buya
знаю где он был на острове Буя
Damn yes you need to
Блин
know you need to
знать надо
read me maybe show me
почитать меня может показать
la Great Tartary yes
ла Великой тартарии да
yes
да
me I have told our SV how much the
меня Я сколько нашим СВ
Heirs of the Great Tartary are
расска Наследники Великой тартарии
not just yes yes the
не просто вот да вот Веды
Slavic-Aryan Vedas are our treasure and the flag
славяно-арийские это скарб наш а флаг
show the flag on which the Vedas
покажи флаг на которых Веды
lie square with the enemy square with the sorcerer
лежат квадрат с ворога квадрат с ворожи
square yes cool aka also symbolism Do
квадрат да прикольно ака ещё символика У
you have Kolovrat Kolovrat is just a
тебя есть Коловрат Коловрат это просто
sun  ours yes I also have such a magazine
солнышко наше да ещё у меня такой журнал
there is a gift to the carols Yes And here in detail
есть коляде дар Да И вот здесь подробно
Well about all the posts about Well about the holidays and
Ну про все посты про Ну про праздники и
here is the most interesting about Dada summer Yes
вот самое интересное о Дада лето Да
creation
сотворение
Yes creation of the world in the Star Temple Vo a
Да сотворение мира в Звёздном храме Во а
yes The most ancient summer calculation Yes
да Самое древнее лето исчисление Да
957 530 year from  time of the gods' appearance
957 530 год от времени появления богов
now yes it goes yes Well
сейчас да идт да
yes yes that's the most such thing already how many
Ну ну да да вот самое такое уже сколько
million years I think we've been
под миллион лет счита тут
living here and then so I still have Well
живём и потом так что у меня ещё А ну
damn everything else there you in the room There
блин всё остальное там вй в комнате Там
in the other there he sleeps I understood amulet bya
в другой там спит у меня понял амулете
Yes at  there are a lot of me in general all shows
бя Да у меня куча вообще вся показы
show such there is cool
показывай такое есть прикольно
square too here with a fortune teller such
квадрат тоже вот с ворожий такого
Cool And what about you  are you filming content
Прикольно А вы что контент снимаете Да
No
нет
no I'm just communicating I communicate with
не я просто общаюсь я общаюсь с
Ukrainians I installed a VPN like I have
украинцами я ставил VPN типа у меня
Ukraine there it says I communicate with Ukrainians
Украина там пишет я общаюсь с украинцами
I ask how do you feel about me a
спрашиваю как вы относитесь ко мне
Russian who lives in America and they
русскому который живёт в Америке и они
somehow
там что-то короче
hang there And what do you think Look
виснут А как ты считаешь Вот смотри
Putin started this war in which
Путин затеял эту войну в которой по сути
he essentially kills the Slavs Aria
он убивает славяна Ария
Well, yes He is a
Ну да Он же
Jew and this
иудей и этот
Medvedev Well, the same thing Volodya
Медведев Ну тоже самое Володи
Mendel Yes, he is
же Мендель Да он
Mendel and everything turns out the same in
Мендель и всё и получается также на
Ukraine Yes So with us in this I see in
Украине да Так у нас в этом вот я вижу в
America they show here  in America too
Америке показывают у нас в Америке тоже
there is Trump Biden they are all yes Well and in
там Трамп байден они всё да Ну а в
Ukraine they also put Mendel right well
Украине они поставили тоже Менделя прям
right president they are not hiding Yes in
ну прям президент не прячутся Да в
Russia the Medels are still hiding yes And in
России ещё прячутся медели да А в
Ukraine they are not
Украине не
hiding everything is already official yes And here
прячутся там всё официально уже да И тут
I will say more yes it turns out in Russia
я больше скажу да получается в России
now  Putin takes Russian men
сейчас Путин берёт русских мужиков
Slavic Aria sends to Ukraine they will kill
Славяно Арию отправляет в Украину убиват
Slavs Ari is one people one people
славяна Ари это же один народ один народ
Slavic
Славяно
Aryan and all sorts of Ramza  the Kadyrovs are
арийский а всякие там рамза кадыровы
just sitting, in short, collecting money for
только сидят короче денежки собирают
themselves and power Yes, and they are happy,
себе и власть Да и радуются
yes Because you know the Slavs, the Aryans, they
да Потому что знаешь славяна Арии они
gave the whole world, gave the whole world,
дали всему миру дали всему миру
Civilization, technology Yes, through God,
Цивилизацию технологии Да через Богом
ours, and now all these
наши а сейчас все эти
peoples They are jealous, apparently, yes,
народы Они завидуют видно да
as if they were not playing this leading
что как бы не они играли эту ведущую
violin and  what are they doing now they
скрипку и сейчас они что делают они
want to do it with their hands
хотят руками
so that there are fewer of us so that we
для того чтобы нас стало меньше чтобы мы
don't reproduce How many children do you have by the
не размножались Сколько у тебя детей
way one for now And how old are you
кстати один пока что А сколько тебе лет
2 is somehow not enough for 2 I have four already
2 как-то мало для 2 у меня четверо уже
I'm 33 I have
мне 33 у меня
four Well also up to 35 We need to  although I
четверо Ну тоже до 35 Надо хотя пятерых
'll try five,
попробовать
I'm 6, you need to catch up with four in 9 years, but
я 6 тебе за 9 лет надо четыре догнать Но
that's a bit complicated, can
это что-то сложновато
your wife handle such a
у тебя жена выдержит такой
pace? Let's hope, and how does she feel
Темп Будем надеяться а она как относится
about five? Yes, it's normal, like now,
к пятерым Да нормально как сейчас
how old is the child,
сколько ребёнку лет годик годик А как
one year old, one year old? And what was the name of one summer, one summer, Leo called it  I
назва одно лето одно лето Лев назвал В
mean Lev, it's a
смысле Лев это
Jewish name, lion Well, damn, I'm a little bit
ж еврейское имя лев Ну блин да что-то я
weak Well, last year I didn't
малёха Ну я в прошлом году ещё не так
know it like now I wanted to
ведал как как сейчас я хотел Добрыня
call him Dobrynya but I called him Lev Well
назвать а назвал Лев Ну Лёва Да ну я
Lyova Well, I suggested different names, well, well, well, well, well, well, I dont know. Yes, baby, well, youve disappointed me. Its the first time Ive met someone who knows everything on chatroulette, you know. Well, damn, its so simple, and to call her name, name Well, you in Slavic Aliski is the key to a person, you wouldn't call your son, for example, a TV, you really wouldn't call your son a cat or a dog there You called him a lion an animal Well, damn, yes, small, not niche, they called people by the name of animals and people of sleep, the Aryans called people by the names of gods Slav there was Yaroslav the one who glorifies Yarilo Miroslav the one who glorifies the world God How can one call SN Aryan named his son Leo the first son thought Well, a protector of the kind of clan Well, I somehow thought so Well, yes, in the Slavic Aryan belief Leo is the protector of the clan Leo is among all Slavs Ariev Yes Lev was right yes here in Rus' Lvov was right But Lev Tolstoy he was Russian don't look eh all these writers what are they  they call them
ээ все вот эти писатели как их называют
Yes, not writers, but
Да не писатели а
writers from the times of the Russian Empire Yes,
писатели времён Российской империи Да
these are all those who were
это все кто
hanging around, all these
шатались все вот эти
liberals were Pushkin, not a Slav,
либеральные были Пушкин не славяна
Aryan Lermontov, not a Slav,
арий Лермонтов не славян
Aryan
арий
Leo
Лев
Tolstoy, a Russian man He
Толстой русский человек Львом не
was not called Leo Damn, well, I certainly got it right
назывался Блин ну я что-то да пригнал
Yes, and the naming ceremony  name
ль Да А имя наречение в обряд имя
naming will take place about name naming ritual
наречение пройдёт о имя наречение обряд
Lev Don't
Лев Не
call them Well, name them
называйте Ну им нарека ите
Slavic-Aryan
славяно-арийские
names here's a way out of the situation Well,
именами вот выход из положения Ну как
the thing is that you branded him as Lev
дело в том что вы на него клеймо Льва
or will they
поставили или у него будут всюду в
write Lev Lev everywhere in his documents they will
документах писать Лев Лев его будут
call him Lev Lev in  school Lev friends
звать Лев лев в школе Лев друзья
Lev you can call him there Yaropolk yes
Лев ты его можешь назвать там ярополк да
and he will be Lev Lyova imagine that
а он будет Лев Лёва представляешь что
your son will be called Lyova teacher
твоего сына будут звать Лёва учительница
at school Lyova
в школе Лёва
Lyovochka this is just this is some kind of disgrace of the
Лёвочка это просто это какой-то позор
Slavic Aryan race Lyovochka Yes what the
Славяно арийского рода Лёвочка Да что
hell did I drive the child away I did something specifically  horse Well
блин прогнал я что-то конкретно коне Ну
yes And is it possible to somehow change it
да А можно как-то поменять
now since you will already change it Well  somehow we
сейчас так как уже поменяешь Ну как-то
need to change Well, they can change him,
надо поменять Ну могут же менять 16 лет
he's 16, he can change him, but before 16,
он-то сможет поменять но до 16 надо
something needs to be done Well, damn, you can ruin a child's life
что-то делать Ну блин это ребёнку жизнь
So, damn,
можно испортить Так ну Львом
call him Leo
назвать блин
Yes, I wanted to call him Dobrynya from the very
Да я хотел Добрыня назвать с самого
beginning, you need to listen to your heart and not  And
начала слушать своё сердце надо а не А
who said Lev Yes, I listened to something to my mother
кто сказал Лев Да я что-то и маме своей
Well, in short,
послушал Ну короче
damn, your mother, your mother chose for your son,
блин мама твоя мама выбирала твоему сыну
no No, I offered different Well, and somehow
не Не ну я предлагал разные Ну и как-то
we Well, the first child somehow Damn, you know
мы Ну первый ребнок как-то Блин знаешь
something like  -that Damn I don't
что-то как-то Блин не
know That is, you couldn't decide without your mother
знаю То есть ты без мамы не мог решить
what to name your heir No, you could
как наследника назвать Да нет мог
Why the hell is grandma still
Почему капец ещ бабушку бабушка
alive grandma yes you could also
живая да ты бы ещё бабушку
ask grandma grandma How should I name my heir
спросил бабушка Как мне моего наследника
Slavic
назвать славяна
Ari she would also say Solomon
Ари она бы ещё Соломон сказала
something drove away this this this is real
чтото прогнал это это это реально
Seriously, it just turns out that you
Серьёзно это просто получается ты на
imposed on him the energy of the egregor not of the
него наложил энергетику эгрегор не
Slavic Aryan people but of the
Славяно арийского народа а
Semitic Slavic names Slavic
семитское имена славянские Славяно
toffee were Prince Svyatoslav Vladimir Japanese
ириски были князь Святослав Владимир япо
Yaroslav what did the Christian RKO ko
Ярослав что сдела христианская рко ко
replace the names gave everyone Greek
заменила имена дала всем греческие
Roman and Jewish names now Ilya
римские и еврейские имена теперь Илья
heel of God or Yahu Yes some Michael
пятка Бога иль яху Да какой-то Михаэль
Gabriel Gavrielovich
Гавриила гавриэлович
Dionysius Yes God of winemaking alcoholism
Дионисий Да Бог виноделия алкоголизма
God of Greek
Бог греческого
alcoholism Well yes and you haven't changed your
алкоголизма Ну да а ты не поменял
passport you can change your passport that
паспорт ты же можешь поменять паспорт то
is  You have a
есть У тебя
son Lev
сын лев
Denisovich I
Денисович Мне
wish you could see in some chronicle
бы блин можешь в какой-то летописи
that Lev
увидеть что Лев
Denisovich was not me I changed my passport when I got into this topic Yes I
Денисович не я был я когда в эту тему
changed my name I changed my name yes
Да имя поменял имя поменял да
the law allows changing
законодательство разрешает менять
your name in Russia you can change it from the age of 16
имя у нас в России можно менять с 16 лет
You  you can
Ты можешь сам типа меня
change your last name yourself like me and you can change your patronymic It seems like it
и фамилию можешь менять отчество Вроде
doesn't change that is Denisovich he will
только не меняется то есть Денисович он
remain
останется
now but you can stop being
теперь но ты можешь перестать быть
Denis [ __ ]
Денисом бля
go What kind of name do you feel like
пройти Како какое имя ты себе чувствуешь
I am so Vedis readers and
Я так Ведис читалки и
which one is suitable
которая подходит
gn
гн
genn once again by letters
генн ещё раз по буквам
de Yan
де Ян
gn d  dejan an I thought I think you
гн д деян ан Я думал думаю что-то ты не
read something wrong from the very beginning  started talking deyan
то почитал с самого начала говорил деян
understood And what does o mean po what I am not
понял А что о означает по что Я не
familiar with this name deytel something like that
знаком с этим именем деятель чтото такое
too
тоже
ti No you are clearly not deyan
ти Нет ты явно не диян
then I do not feel such
тогда я не чувствую такую
energy And what other names are you
энергетику А какие ещё имена
considering for yourself yes I have exactly
Рассматриваешь для себя да у ме именно
words Slavic there Come on now
слов есть Славянский там Давай сейчас
Come on  now let's choose Here take it
Давай сейчас давай выберем Вот возьми
Open exactly the words on the seventh page
Открой именно слов на седьмой странице
the seventh name from the top Well come on
седьмое сверху имя А ну давай
with It's
с
not real I chose names like that too the
Не реально я так выбирал тоже
thing is that the Slavic method of
имена это дело в том что Славский метод
drawing lots used to be called as it was volkh
жребия называется раньше как было волх
Yes he wrote names on the bones and threw out
Да он писал имена на костях и выкидывал
whichever would fall into the circle  and
которое в круг попадёт то и попадало
now you can guess on books
сейчас на книгах можно
Dava come on and in that and in that
гадать Дава давай и в том и в том именно
word se ni so
слове сеь ни
Well
так Ну
here
тут
p
п
so the seventh name by Well here like a
так седьмое имя по Ну тут типа
preface Well here here what names
предисловие Ну вот вот вот Какие имена
Come on Boguslav once wake up Slav 2 Boleslav
Давай Богуслав раз буди Слав 2 болеслав
3 Breslav 4 Burislav 5  Braslav 6 top
3 бреслав 4 бурислав 5 Браслав 6 верху
Slav se so top Slav A well let's
Слав се так верху Слав А ну давай во
tell fortunes in the second word like
втором именно слове погадаем
this Seventh Well this is it  seventh page right
так Седьмая Ну вот это седьмая страница
away Let's go to the seventeenth
сраз Давай семнадцатую
then and not this This is not exactly a word
тогда а не это Это не именно слово у
you have these are just sensible words no no
тебя это просто толковые слова нет нет
this is exactly a word exactly a
это именно слово именно
word yes yes Well then Yes where are
слово да да Ну дальше Да где
the names so Yes here is a ston Gregor de come on
имена так Да тут стона грегор де давай
so
так
look take Open the thirty-third
смотри возьми Открой тридцать третью
page and go for now  no you won't meet
страницу и иди пока не не встретишь
any name any name thirty third
Какое Любое имя тридцать третью
page open thirty third
страницу открывай тридцать третью
page thirty third well thirty
страницу тридцать третью ну тридцать
third and let's look from above what
третью и давай сверху вот смотрим какую
first we will meet in this or in the next
первую встретим в этой или в следующей
Yes what name so here some name is there
Да какое имя так тут имя какое-то есть
no go to thirty fourth let's
нету перели на тридцать четвёртую давай
look thirty fourth
смотрим тридцать четвёртое
so
так
Yan tour stop stop
Янь тур стоп стоп
stop gods a la this is not it so let's give the
стоп боги а ла это не то так давай
thirty-
тридцать
fifth name stop stop stop
пятую имя стоп стоп стоп
name not parama don't give the thirty-sixth
имя не парама не давай тридцать шестое
Let's do it this way the first name that we will
Давай вот так первое имя которое нам
meet now it came to us
теперь встретится оно и пришло нам
Let's do it this way I also chose
Давай я так тоже выбирал
Manu Manu name about parents  humanity
Ману Ману имя про родитель человечество
son of dazhbog for about day of dazhbog
сын дажбога за о день дажбога
yes not some Tajik We have here Tajik
да не какой-то таджикско У нас тут таджи
Well, come on, come on, Tajik  Let's go
Ну давай хорошо давай таджи Давай
on to think that he is
дальше подумает что Армянин
some kind of Armenian No, well, in Europe, like
какой-то Не ну в Европе типа
somewhere in Slovakia or somewhere like that, maybe let's go Yes, we'll
где-то Словакии или где-то так может
get to these very names Let's go maybe there are some where
дойдём Давай может там есть где-то
right now the letters will end And it
именно сейчас закончатся буквы Да и
will begin Let's go to the end  alphabet
начнётся Давай давай в конец алфавита
we run Oh now there will be names Oh I am
бежим О вот сейчас будут имена О я
now nano exactly words Yes
теперь нано именно слов Да следующее
next next exactly word beginning in exactly
дальше именно слово начина во именно
word here it is
слово вот оно
in in seventh we are looking for fourth
в в седьмой ищем четвёртая
fifth sixth seventh here is seventh so looking for the
пятая шестая седьмая вот седьма так ищ
seventh name which here are heroes here from above from
седьмое имя которое вот герои вот сверху
above first Vlad spirit mil good Vlad
сверху первое Влад дух мил добро Влад
fourth e good dobrogo dobrozhan fifth good
четвёртое э доброго доброжан пятое добро
life sixth dobromil seventh good
жизнь шестое добромиль седьмое добро
mil with us
мил у нас
T more you see good top
Т больше видишь добро верхо
sladu rodolad
сладу родолад
By the way, do you cut your nails
Ты кстати ногти подстригаешь
Not yet and that's right with us I
Пока нет и правильно у нас Я то
cut them because I have
подстригаю потому что у меня работа
such a job Here in America I can't And so it
такая Тут в Америке Я не могу А так это
is  invented cut nails These are the ones that
ж придумали стрич ногти Это те которые
cut the flesh
обрезают плоть
damn something
блин что-то
Yare
Яре
such Damn I don't like making mistakes and
таком Блин так не нравится ошибаться и
such mistakes are like well well you
такие ошибки как бы ну ну
see you as a man should accept this
видишь ты как мужчина должен принять эту
mistake and correct it well you are
ошибку и исправлять это ну ты несёшь за
responsible for it not someone
неё ответственность не кто-то за тебя
made the decision for you Yes mom advised Yes well it is
принял решение Да мама советовала Да ну
not mom who is responsible for your son Well I
не мама ответственна за твоего сына Ну я
mean that I  I would advise with
имею в виду то что я бы советовал бы с
relatives because we are still new and
родными потому что мы всё-таки новый а
wife What is the name
жену Как зовут
Daria Daria is normal it is also a Slavic
Дарья Дарья нормально ещё это Славяно
Aryan
арийское
name yes Well his dad is
имя да Ну у него папа
Jewish I see you hit the jackpot
еврей Я вижу ты джекпот сорвал
and your son is a
и сын
lion you know how to make people laugh of course Well that's
лев умеешь ты рассмешить конечно Ну это
life yes you see life sends
же жизнь да видишь жизнь посылает
we have different samples Well, you see, this is
нам пробы разные Да ну это видишь это
your karmic Cross that you must now
твой кармический Крест его должен теперь
bear But what your son called a lion, you see
пронести Но то что сын лев назвал видишь
I now understand why That's when you
Я теперь понял почему ли Вот когда ты
say His dad is a Jew, it turns out that
скажешь У него папа еврей получается на
two egregors fought for his son, the
за сына за сына билось два эгрегора
Slavic-Aryan and
славяно-арийский и
dad's Well  papin
папин Ну папин
won That is, you as a man did not
выиграл То есть ты как мужчина не
show your masculine essence like fire a
проявил свою мужскую сущность как огонь
man should set the tone but not
мужчина должен задавать тон да не
women should And then the wife gets mom
женщины должны А тут получает жена мама
picked out a name for your son Well, I also
подбирали твоему сыну имя Ну я тоже с
consulted with them Well, well, yeah  that's what well
ними советовался Ну как бы ну да вот то
how
что ну как
would I still here it's time exactly these words
бы я ещё вот пора именно словы эти не
I generally didn't really know somehow something I
знал я вообще толком как-то что-то я
even somehow generally And how
даже как-то вообще А как ты
long have you been in this topic Well a year of
давно как ты давно в этой теме Ну год
knowing how to howl at true
позна как выл на истинные
knowledge Well this  how did he also
знания Ну этот как его ну тоже читать
start reading and studying and looking at
начал так изучать смотреть там
all sorts of T's there's also a familiar woman there's
всякие Т тоже знако женщина там
one there on the application he was repairing washing machines
одна там на заявке ремонтировал стиралки
also something like that in passing I heard something well
тоже что-то так мельком что-то услышал
VST I
нучи вст
also found where there were swastikas as
нашл тоже где вот свастики были как
if some Slavic-Aryan Vedas
будто какие-то славяно-арийские Веды
I remember  I found it somehow I was so
помню нашёл вот как-то меня так
interested and started to study
заинтересовала и начал изучать
read
читать
watch
смотреть
such Rovki are there any you do
такое Ровки есть какие-то у тебя нет
n't have any
нет никаких
no and the room
нет а комна
rustles something you
что-то шуршит у тебя
constantly say why don't you decorate the room with
постоянно говорю почему комнату не одоби
different amulets decorate
оберегами разными
How exactly decorate - well you
одоби Как именно одоби - это ну ты
did it  in Slavic
сделал по-славянски
odabrati is
одабрати
some Jewish
это какое-то еврейское
word to paint walls with runes, for example, so
слово расписать рунами стены например ну
that they become amulets.
чтоб обереги
Yes, I need to try it. I want to learn all the light.
да Надо попробовать хочу все свет ную
All the light. How many
грамоту все свет грамоту сколько там
letters are there, by the way, do you know? No. There are a lot of them.
букв кстати знаешь нет Да там их куча
the light of literacy is also what the
светя грамота - это тоже то Что прячут
Slavs of the Aryans hide from us because they
От нас славяна Ариев потому что нам
tell us that some Greeks and Cyril and
говорят что какие-то греки да Кирилл и
Methodius and their students brought us
Мефодий Да ихние ученики принесли нам
which we ran there barefoot and did
которые мы там голые босы бегали читать
not know how to read and write Yes wisdom and how many years has it
писать Не умели Да мудрость а скоко лет
existed on Ari and how much  Greek
на Ари существует и сколько греческая
civilization
цивилизация
Compare Therefore yes world literacy
Сравни Поэтому да всеясветная грамота -
is the ladis of the Slavic Aryan
это ладис Славяно арийской
literature of wisdom Yes each letter is
литературы мудрости Да каждая буквица -
now what did they do they took for us
это сейчас они что сделали они взяли нам
simplified the letter what did the Greeks do they
упростили бук что сделали греки они
took our world literacy threw out
взяли нашу все свет ную грамоту выкинули
most of the letters and left us with some
большинство букв и оставили нам каких-то
30 with a piece  yes That
30 с кусочком да
is, what is it They stole sounds from us
То есть а что такое Они украли у нас
because each letter Previously, Yes
звуки потому что каждая буква Раньше Да
denoted a sound and denoted
обозначала звук и обозначал
the essence of the divine essence And now
сущность божественную сущность А сейчас
what have they done to us Do you know
что они нам сделали Ты знаешь откуда
where the letter A is the first in the
почему буква а первая в
alphabet
алфавите
No, A and B Look, this came from
нет Вот А и Б Смотри это ж пошло из
Greek Alpha and Beta the Greeks have Alpha and
греческого Альфа и Бета у греков Альфа и
Beta
Бета
and they transferred to us Slavs A and B A  the
и перенесли они нам славянам А и Б А у
Greeks Alpha and Beta came from the Semites the
греков Альфа и Бета пошло от семитов
first
первая
letter of
буква
Hebrew is Aleph hence Alpha you understand
иврита - это Алеф отсюда Альфа понимаешь
this is the ancient Phoenician alphabet was
это древний Финикийский алфавит был
the letter Alf the Greeks took it from
буква Альф его взяли греки себе от
the Semites and now they gave us the Slavs instead of
семитов и теперь дали нам славян вместо
our world literacy we have the first
нашей всеясветной грамоты у нас первы
letter
буква
AF hence the
АФ отсюда
alphabet alphabetbet Alpha Beta you  you understand
алфавит алфабет Альфа Бета ты понимаешь
how they have long penetrated our
как они давно проникли в наш
egregor This is how we write, they tell us Yes, with
эгрегор Вот так мы пишем нам говорят Да
Cyrillic letters, we begin
кириллические буквами мы начинаем
to think So it turns out to be
задумываться Так это получается
Greek letters Yes, with corrupted ones,
греческие буквицы Да испорченные
we begin to dig even deeper, so these are
начинаем ещё глубже копать так это
Semitic letters
семитские буквицы
from ancient
с древней
Palestine But the letter there is also AC,
Палестины А вот буквица там же тоже АС
gods, lead, speak good, here  we had the
боги веди глаголи добро вот у нас было у
Slavs Aryans ABCs Veda it was
славяна Ариев Азбуки веде это была
Glagolitic And they gave us
глаголица А нам дали
Cyrillic there everything Like us a b c g everything
кириллицу там всё Как у нас а б в г всё
children I don't understand it's not just a b Letter
дети не понимаю это не просто а б Буква
A they disguised their
А они так замаскировали своего
alif like that Damn, how can I fix it
алифа Блин а как мне исправить
Damn, well that's it Go look  go where u  you there
Блин ну это Иди смотри иди Где у вас там
migration or Who issues these names here the
миграционка или Кто выдаёт вот эти имена
registry office what is it called here here
закс как оно называется у вас вот
Clarify How can I change the name of the child
Уточняй Как можно поменять имя ребнку
because years old himself Maybe I can change it but
потому что лет сам себе Может поменять а
I think in some Maybe
я думаю в некоторых Может к какому-то
contact some lawyer Yes clarify How can I
юристу обратись Да уточни Как можно
change the name of the child there is
поменять имя ребёнка есть
such a thing  it's complicated Well, damn, I mean
такое это сложно Так блин я имею в виду
with my family and all this
с роднёй и всё это
somehow, and that is, wait, that is, you are a
как-то а то есть подожди То есть ты
man now Are you worried about what
мужчина сейчас Переживаешь что подумает
your mother will think, your wife No, no, no, I'm
твоя мама твоя жена Нет не ну нет нет я
not worried about this, no, no
не переживаю за это не нет
It all depends on the strength of your spirit  If
Всё зависит от силы твоего духа Если
your spirit is weak Yes, you will think how to
твой дух слаб Да ты будешь думать как
explain this to your family What will your family
объяснить это роднее А что родня
think And if you are a man with a strong spirit,
подумает А если ты мужчина сильный духом
you will come and
ты придёшь и
say my son will bear a Slavic
скажешь мой сын будет носить славяна
Aryan
арийское
name I
имя я так
decided so it will begin and why and why did I
решил начнётся а почему а зачем я так
decide so I am a man what does the word man mean
решил Я мужчина что означает слово
You know
Знаешь
man Yes it consists of husband and
мужчина Да он состоит из мужа и
Chin it is husband hence
Чина это муж отсюда
courageous If a man can not
мужественный Если мужчина не может
say that yes I decided so I take responsibility for it
сказать что да я так решил я беру за это
This is my Heir he
ответственность Это мой Наследник он не
will not be a lion  Denisovich
будет львом денисовиче
damn how will this affect the little one damn
блин на самого малого как это блин
you will get rid
повлияет Ты отвяжешься
of the Slavic Aryan normal
к Славяно арийского нормальному
egregor this is
эгрегору этот
like the first year of life let's say yes
ка то что первый год жизни допустим да
they called him by one name
его назвали одним именем
then what And what are you like Here you can name
потом и что А ты какие Вот ты можешь имя
in speech Yes you were called there for 30 years
на речь Да тебя называли там 30 лет
Denis and then  you will be the top Slav and
Денис а потом будешь верхо Слав и
normally look always in the tradition Yes
нормально посмотри всегда в традиции Да
when the naming was Yes changed the
когда имен наречение было Да менял
person's name normally he joins the
человек имя нормально он приобщаться к
egregor worse that he 2 years will awaken
эгрегору хуже что он 2 года пробудит
Leo or years prot Leo we tighten the
Львом или года прот львом затягиваем тем
more he is in that egregor the egregor
больше он в том эгрегор эгрегор
penetrates into him completely his cells
проникает в него полностью его клетки
are saturated with energy  foreign people
пропитываются энергетикой чужого народа
and then he goes like this and says No no
а потом он такой оп и говорит Не нет
Dad I'll go and worship foreign gods
Папа я пойду чужим богам поклонюсь
and for him they're not foreign it's just his
а для него это не чужие просто это его
egregor then that knocks on his heart and
тогда эгрегор тот стучит ему в сердце и
says Leo you're from our people
говорит Лев ты из нашего народа
Yes Yahva bless you what Perun
Да яхва тебя благословит какой перун
What welding What ra  this is some kind of
Какой сварок Какой ра это какие-то
fiction Come on I believe that you are a man
выдумки Давай я верю что ты мужчина
who can handle it there is a go in your
который справится есть у тебя го в
eyes I  I'll go because I need to, you
глазах я пойду потому что мне надо у нас
rarely meet a sane person here,
редко встретишь здравомыслящего таго
you know, the thing is
знаешь дело в том
that the Universe brings people together for a reason.
что Вселенная сводит людей не просто так
We appear in each other's lives and carry
Мы появляемся в жизни друг друга и несём
some kind of Sign. You need to be able to read these
какое-то Знамение надо уметь читать эти
signs and accept
знамения и принимать от
peace from the Universe.
Вселенной мир
You, like me, have
тебе как я
broken away
отрывался
now.  zant
теперь не зант
until
до сих
now it was bomb you not a single
пор это было бомбически вам ни один
blogger of such funny content with
блогер такого контента ржачного с
Russians will not ask Aro knows everything with anyone
русскими не запит Аро знает всё с любым
we will find obligatory
мы найдём об
yaz rer from will capture you letter on y
яз рер от захватит вас пись на й
Telegram right now he
Telegram прям зараз он
AK this is very and very important YouTube takes
АК це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scarg or  in your ban and very
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
many videos I do not show to people sometimes I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali operational links
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
are written right now and while there in telegra we will
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
see videos there is also interesting and useful
окрим вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry for you
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
constant operational  links
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that che will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
write L
пиши L